<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filipino :: Ray&#39;s Recipe&#39;s</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/filipino/index.html</link>
    <description>Foreword&#xD;A collection of Filipino Recipe’s. Pork and Coconut, and intense savoury goodness are normal here! personally my favorite food with japanese&#xA;Ginataang Ginataang Manok&#xA;Adobo Fried BBQ</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/filipino/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ginataang Manok</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/filipino/ginataang_manok/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/filipino/ginataang_manok/index.html</guid>
      <description>Foreword&#xD;This is the Recipe i use to make Ginataang Manok, also called a Chicken Coconut Stew. As always, keep in mind i go alot by feeling! adjust it to your liking. The list of spices used will be at the very end if you dont have them at home!&#xA;Tip&#xD;Get some Nice fatty Coconut milk, i’d say around 40% upwards. This dish, as well as many other versions have alot of freedom! as long as the core ingridients are correct&#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumpia Shanghai</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/filipino/lumpia/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/filipino/lumpia/index.html</guid>
      <description>Foreword&#xD;This is the Recipe i use to make Lumpia Shanghai, Bascially the Filipino verion of Pork Spring Rolls. They are fairly simple to make, they just take time to prepare! this is for around 500g of meat.&#xA;Shopping list! Pork Mince Spring Roll Wrappers Carrots n onions Oyster Sauce Egg’s (optional: Cashew Nuts) Making the filling 1st. Cut 1 Carrot and 1 Onions finely. or you can use a grater. 2nd. in a bowl add the Veg, 500g Pork mince, Potato or Corn Starch. 0.5 Tsb Coriander Powder. 1 Tsb Chicken Powder (or borth powder), 1 Tsb Garlic Powder, 1 Tsb Salt, 1 Tsb Pepper, 1 Tsb Sugar, 2 TBsp Oyster sauce, and finally 2 Eggs 3rd. Mix it until its all nice and combined 4th. Take a Wrapper and add around 1 TBsp of the mixture and roll it in. close the rolls with Water or egg wash if you feel fancy Details&#xD;Fold the sides in, and then roll it downwards, make a “cigar”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>