<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Korean :: Ray&#39;s Recipe&#39;s</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/korean/index.html</link>
    <description>This is a new chapter.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/korean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gochujang Shrimp Pasta with Cream Sauce</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/korean/gochujang-shrimp-cream-sauce/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/korean/gochujang-shrimp-cream-sauce/index.html</guid>
      <description>Foreword&#xD;This Recipe is for a simple but Flavourful cream sauce! its best with Shrimp, but you could do it with chicken.&#xA;Shopping list! Shrimps Gochujang Paste Heavy Cream the Rest is prolly in your Pantry Preprep Season the Shrimp with: Garlic Powder, Paprika, Cayenne pepper (or chilli powder) Salt, and a bit of oil Chop some Garlic (if you dont have it, garlic powder) and dice an Onion. Time to Cook. 1st. Cook the Shrimp for 4-5 Minutes, and set them aside. While thats happening, cook some Pasta of your choice 2nd. In the same Pot you cooked the Shrimp in. cook some diced Onion and garlic until soft. 3rd. Add the Gochujang Paste, stirr, and add the Cream, let it cook for a 2-3 minutes. then add some pasta water. 4th. Finally add back your Shrimp back in, and also add the Pasta you cooked! Note&#xD;if you like it cheesy, you can also add chese, but i dont like it much personally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC (Korean Fried Chicken)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/korean/fried-chicken/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/korean/fried-chicken/index.html</guid>
      <description>Foreword&#xD;This Recipe is for Some great fried Chicken, there will be 2 Seasoning Variants, one with Sauce, one without. If you want to make the Sauce along with it, just keep the Seasoning simple.&#xA;Shopping list! Chicken Breast (thighs are hard to get here :( )) Flour Baking powder For the optional Sauce Gochujang Ketchup Soy Sauce. Starch syrup the Rest is prolly in your Pantry Prepping the Chicken 1st. Cut the Chicken into Equal pieces. Then season the Chicken with Salt, Pepper, Garlic, Paprika, and Chilli powder. 2nd. Prepare a rather thick batter. a 1:1 Ratio of Flour and Water. add a Tsp of Baking Power and the seasoning. you kind of want to aim for a thinner pancake batter 3rd. Mix the Chicken with the batter 4th. Grab a Bowl with a lid, tupperwear. etc and put some Seasoned flour in there. (Flour, Baking powder, and the Spices). add some pieces and shake it. Time to fry the Chicken 1st. Heat up the Oil, if you are unsure if the Oil is ready, drop a piece of Flour from the container in, if it rises up in 3 seconds, its perfect! 2nd. then add the Chicken in Batches, dont overcrowed the Chicken. stirr it in the beginning so it doesnt stick. they will be ready once they float up or after around 7 mins. when they are golden brown. And thats it! serve it like that or with Rice! but….if you want a nice sauce to go with it! keep reading. Time for the Sauce 1st. in a bowl, add 1 Tsp of Gochujang, 5 Tbsp of Ketchup 3-4, 4 Tbsp of Sugar. and 1 Tsp of Garlic Powder. mix mix mix 2nd. put the Sauce in a pan. heat it up, add the chicken and cover it. Take it out and its done too! simple.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>